https://salonquip.com.au/privacy-policy/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
What your privacy means to us
SalonQuip has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of your personal information provided by you when visiting and interacting with this website. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following information discloses the gathering of information and dissemination practices for this website.
SalonQuip recognises the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site.
This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs and may be updated from time to time.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit the SalonQuip website, you may provide us with two types of information:
A. Personal information you knowingly choose to disclose to us that is collected on an individual basis, and
B. Website use information collected as you browse our website.
1. PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE
Registration Information
When you register for any of our products, services or electronic communications you will provide us with information about yourself.
Credit Card Information
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then the gateway stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After this your purchase transaction information is deleted.
If you use a credit card on this site the transactions will be processed via the SecurePay Secure Payment System. Your credit card details will not be stored unless you authorise us to do so all details are then stored securely by SalonQuip.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
2. WEBSITE USE INFORMATION
Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilises a standard technology called “Cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through Cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent on our website, and the websites visited just prior to and after our website.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of:
administering our business activities;
providing the products and services you requested;
to process your payment;
to monitor the use of the service;
to market, promote and improve our content and service offerings;
to customize our site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes.
This will help to improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.
Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.
SalonQuip may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter.
What Are Cookies?
A Cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for Cookies. Each website can send its own Cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to
access the Cookies it has already sent to you, not the Cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept Cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive Cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse Cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse Cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function effectively when viewed by the users. A Cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
As you visit and browse our website, the site uses Cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use Cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our website and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your Cookies.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
Sharing and Selling Information
We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that will uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at accounts@salonquip.com.au
What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the public.
What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other website are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.
Our Commitment to Data Security:
Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in Australia. The laws on holding personal data in the Commonwealth of Australia may differ to the laws of other countries. To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may
include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postcode, age level).
Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
A Special Note about Children
Children must not use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.
Acquisition or Changes in Ownership
In the event that the website (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.
Policy Modifications
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
Copyright © 2020 SALONQUIP PTY LTD
NEW
EQUIPMENT
BEAUTY MACHINES
BRUSH
GALVANIC
HIGH FREQUENCY
HOT TOWEL WARMERS
VOLUME (Y)
ACRYLIC POWDERS (POLYMERS)
PRIMER & LIQUIDS (MONOMERS)
